♪ YOU'RE STILL IN THE SHOWER ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GONNA GO ♪
♪ I WISH I HAD THE POWER ♪
♪ TO MAKE THIS HOUSE
FEEL MORE LIKE HOME ♪
♪ I WON'T SLEEP A MINUTE ♪
♪ LEAVE THE
LIGHT ON BY THE BED ♪
♪ THE BED YOU
SHOULD BE IN, YEAH ♪
♪ IT'S NOT HOW
IT'S SUPPOSED TO END ♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHERE I STARTED ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
WHERE MY HEART IS ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'LL SEE YOU WHEN I SEE YOU ♪
♪ IT HURTS, YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ CAUSE MAYBE
YOU'LL COME RUNNING ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE DONE BEING ALONE ♪
♪ I SWEAR I'LL WAIT FOREVER ♪
♪ IF IT MEANS NOT LETTING GO ♪
♪ I'LL PUT YOU UNDER PRESSURE ♪
♪ WERE YOU SCARED
OF GETTING CLOSE? ♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHERE I STARTED ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
WHERE MY HEART IS ♪
♪♪♪
♪ ALL THESE BRIDGES
THAT WE'RE BURNING ♪
♪ TABLES THAT WE'RE TURNING ♪
♪ I WON'T LET THIS GO ♪
♪ TILL I'M IN THE GROUND ♪
♪ PROMISES YOU'RE BREAKING ♪
♪ PARTS OF ME YOU'RE TAKING ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW MYSELF ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE NOT AROUND ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW MYSELF ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE NOT AROUND ♪
♪♪♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHERE I STARTED ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
WHERE MY HEART IS ♪
♪♪♪